# Travis Manship

## **CONTACT**

Mobile: (325) 440-9462

Email/Skype: tmansdev@gmail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced, Responsible and Passionate Full stack/Blockchain engineer. Always focusing to business value and customer view and love to work with Team and Customers. For 10 years I implemented a lots of customer requirements and made significant contributes to business values. Recently focusing on blockchain smart contract/dApp implementation using solidity/rust/cadence and web3 technologies.

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Restful API implementation Frontend UI Implementation Code review & Testing

3<sup>rd</sup> party API Integration Smart Contract Development DevOps

System Analysis & Design Web3 Integration Networking

DB Design & SQL Arbitrage Bot Cloud Service

Hotel/Flight Booking System Project Planning & Management

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Neusis May 2012 - Feb 2017

#### Web/Mobile Developer

- Responsible to implement web based solutions/tools using react.js, vue.js and angular 1/2
- Responsible to implement various mobile apps using React Native
- Responsible to implement backend logic, Restful/GraphQL APIs, 3<sup>rd</sup> party API integration using Golang/Node.js

Clarus R & D Mar 2017 - Feb 2020

Fullstack Engineer

- Responsible to lead developers to build hotel/flight reservation system and design architecture/database/security, integrated APIs and managed project schedule and delivery using golang and nodejs
- Responsible to implement business logic, backend APIs and security part of ticket reservation system and Tax credit service using golang
- Responsible to implement frontend part of hotel/flight reservation system and tax credit service using React.js and vue.js.
- Responsible to implement test cases for backend logic and react components.

## GigLabs Jan 2020 - Dec 2022

## Fullstack/Blockchain Engineer

- Implemented NFT marketplace, staking and raffle smart contract using solidity on Ethereum.
- Responsible to design database, implement backend APIs, integrate web3 in backend and dApp side
- Implemented Game-Fi and NFT Staking contract using Rust and Anchor framework on Solana
- Research on Dexes and Implemented FlashLoan Arbitrage bot contract on Ethereum
- Implemented Game-Fi smart contract using cadence and web3 integration on Flow
- Implemented test scripts for smart contract functions and backend APIs
- Responsible to make documentation for APIs using docusaurus etc

#### **EDUCATION**

2008 – 2012 Beijing Institute of technology, Computer Science(Bachelor's Degree)

#### TECH GRID

Golang(6)	React.js/Next(5)	Solidity(3)
Node.js(6)	Vue.js/Nuxt(4)	Rust(2)
Javascript(8)	Angular.js(4)	Cadence(2)
SQL(6)	CSS/SCSS(6)	Web3/Ethers(4)
Python(3)	HTML5/ES6,7(8)	Hardhat/Truffle(4)
Typescript(4)	WebRTC(3)	Anchor, Metaplex, SPL(2)
Php/Laravel(4)	WebSocket(5)	EVM/Solana/Flow/Near(4)
Java(5)	gRPC(1)	AWS/GCP/Azure(5)
C/C++(6)	Bootstrap/Material	Docker/Kubernates(4)
	UI/Tilewind(6)	